There are two links beneath this video.
The first one of which
is where you give me your Instagram URL
and your website,
and I get in there and I critique it,
which I'm about to do right now to 15
people.
The second link is an offer to a promotion
that I'm running that I'm going to take
offline too soon because it's an
outrageous offer that's far too cheap.
But don't click on that one yet. Instead,
give me the next few minutes to go over
these 15 random profiles
that I've actually got ChatGPT to pick at
random, so you
know that I'm not picking them because
they're good or they're bad or whatever.
And you see if the advice
that I give these businesses would suit
you enough to
join my program. And if not,
that's also completely fine.
So these were picked by ChatGPT.
As you can see, I asked them to,
and I got it to
hide their email addresses.
Let's begin with Hamza. Get Stronk.
Not sure on that, not mad on that.
Fitness that fits you.
Get Stronk. Look, to begin with,
I don't know who you are, so
that should be
your personal brand. Now,
if your name's Hamza,
that's quite a cool name.
So you should be like Hamza whatever.
This picture is never going to represent
your brand better than you.
Got a good beard going on. If this
is going to be who represents your brand
and
content,
why does it not represent your brand up
here?
This just isn't something I want to
follow.
That looks like an elephant falling over
on a treadmill.
That's not what I'm buying into.
It's not an elephant that's going to turn
up and
PT me online. Now,
you should have made your bio shorter
here, so this bit doesn't
have to be that. In real life
and online coaching.
Let me tell you now,
the amount of people on the internet
is so much bigger than
the amount of people that
are going to coach you through your real
life.
All your marketing online should aim
towards getting people as an online
client.
Some people will find out where you train.
Let's have a look.
Think eh.
This kind of video actually really pisses
me off.
Are you tired of your chicken breast
tasting eh?
Just like stringy and overcooked
and kind of gross.
Well,
here's three mistakes you're probably
making.
I don't like when people say, "Here
are three mistakes.
Here are three mistakes you're probably
making." Just get into it, and what's the
outcome that I want from this?
You should say something like,
"How to make your
chicken taste better."
That could be like a statement hook.
Then the next thing is,
if you're anything like me
and you want to stay in shape
and stay relatively lean,
we have to eat a lot of protein,
which means a lot of
chicken. But there's a problem.
That chicken can taste stringy,
disgusting, and
rank. So let me give you some ways
that we can make it better.
Then you give them number one, number two,
number three.
Because a lot of the time people do get
drawn into going, "Here's five ways that
you can improve your squat. Number one,
raise your heels." Don't know why
I'm speaking in accent. But I'm like, bro,
if that's such a good point, just make
it its own video,
where it could've been like,
if you're someone that struggles to
sit deep in a squat, here's a hack
that you may not have thought about.
Raising your heels artificially creates
dorsiflexion in the ankle, and that means
bla, bla, bla.
Then rather than giving me five things
and taking five topics and
kind of giving them to me shit,
just give me one good one,
and that's five reels
instead of one. But let me listen.
And how to fix it. First mistake,
bit of a hot take, the breast is too big.
The thicker the breast is, the-
Okay, [chuckles] if the first point
is the breast is too big.
Do you ever struggle with sometimes the
breast being too big? Not like that.
I mean with your chicken.
There's some fun here.
There's some banter
that you've just overlooked a little bit.
Less evenly it'll cook
when you actually put it on a heat source.
So there's two options to reduce this.
One,
go ahead and slice it into a cutlet
significantly smaller so it's going to
cook evenly.
Okay,
so you've picked as the first thing to
tell me
about that if the chicken
is too big to cut it in half.
Do you understand that
if I'm watching this
and I'm getting to this point and
I've listened to your introduction,
I'm like, "Yeah, come on bro,
tell me," your
first point, no offense,
is just a bit shit.
On both sides.
You also have more surface area to season.
Option two, take a mallet
and beat your meat.
Again, you've said beating the meat here,
and there's no banter.
When it comes to getting in shape,
it's important that you beat your meat,
and also
to appreciate that sometimes breasts can
be too big. Not like that.
I mean with chicken. Let me explain.
First of all, if your chicken's too big,
cut it in half.
More surface area for seasoning.
Second of all, beat your meat.
Yeah, in the kitchen. Yeah,
when your friends are here. Yeah,
whatever.
Not like that. This is what I'm saying.
There are points here
that we've just kind of overlooked,
and we could've delivered
that a lot quicker.
And then you're probably going to be like,
"Oh, what if I don't have a hammer?" Fry
pan. If it worked for Flynn Ryder,
it works for us.
See, there's a bit of banter there.
And then you make it smart like, "Oh,
but I don't have a fry pan," in which case
you probably shouldn't be watching this
video.
But if you don't have a fry pan,
John Daniels.
Unwrap,
and we've got a beautiful cutlet here.
It's going to be so much easier to cook.
Mistake number two,
you're not salting your chicken.
So take whatever salt you want
and generously, I mean
generously, like four finger pinches.
Now I could explain to you how animal
proteins are 70% water and that means-
Yeah,
so I feel like we could've just made
that a little bit better if I'm honest,
but it's not terrible.
I just think we could've come out with
eating chicken is really important.
Here's ways to make it easier.
Today we're going to make a cocktail with
Strawberry Monster.
So instead of ice we're going to use
frozen-
With this one, why would be my question.
Now we try the gel.
Today we're going to make a cocktail with
Strawberry Monster.
So instead of ice we're going to use
frozen fruit.
What's the problem here?
Like I've had Strawberry Monster.
Now I have my own energy drink business
and let me tell you this, Monster is
amazing. It tastes delicious. Love it.
But never have I had a can and gone, "Hmm,
I wish this was with ice and with
fruit." So I don't understand the problem
it's solving.
Okay, I think it's strawberry
and orange flavor.
I mean-
Don't care.
I want you to imagine we're going to go
through the next few reels like
I've never seen you before,
which eight billion people haven't.
I found these at the grocery store.
Don't care.
Now I was recently on a road trip to
Montreal.
Don't care.
Today we're testing Truly's high protein-
Have you ever wondered how can I piss off
every single South Asian person I know?
Good hook.
Under $10. Today we are testing-
Don't care.
So if we can get hooks in front of people
that they
care about, like the chicken one.
That's why it's done best.
That's why it's one of your pinned posts,
right? Oh, it's not a pinned post.
Are you tired of your chick-
So you haven't posted since October 21st,
2025.
It's 11 weeks ago, brother.
I'll tell you why people don't post.
Because what they're doing isn't working.
So if you get that working.
Look, I would go to your website
and give you some feedback,
but let's do a deal.
If you can't be bothered to post content,
I can't be bothered to go to your
website. Moving on. Edward.
Discover Paragon.
Paragon Studio.
Bespoke sustainable gym products.
Made in the UK with premium natural
materials. Okay.
I'm going to... Interesting.
20,000 followers. Interesting.
Just breathe it in.
Let the still-
Tonight we're hosting Paragon Studio's
first ever supper
club.
Is it a studio or is it gym products?
I'm kind of trying to figure out what's
going on here.
Forget what you think gym equipment should
look like.
Balance becomes strength.
I'm a bit lost here, if I'm honest.
Like the equipment looks good, but
is this a
club? I'm confused. Paragon Studio.
So is it a studio where you can buy home
equipment? Okay, luxury gym equipment.
I don't really know here.
I'm kind of a bit Confused.
Now, the sustainable aspect of it, cool.
But for me,
I would go in on the aesthetics.
And again,
I don't know much about gym equipment, but
rather than being sustainable gym
products,
maybe just go to war with traditional
dumbbells. You could go, "Technogym,
this is ugly, this is ugly, this is ugly,
this is ugly. Our stuff isn't.
Your home is a beautiful place, and it
shouldn't be tarnished by fitness
equipment that doesn't have the aesthetic
vibe
that it needs. At Paragon,
we go with equipment you can be proud of."
Yeah, I'm
just not really sure what's going on here,
to be honest.
And that is a slight problem, I'm afraid.
Angela, let's get into it.
The high-performing team strategist.
Enabling CEOs and directors to reclaim one
day per week to grow their business.
Okay. Official. Not sure on official here,
if I'm completely honest.
Let's have a look.
Hi, I'm Angela Hodgson,
and I'm sharing some very exciting news.
Energy absolutely fizzles,
or it does for me.
Fizzling, getting excited, get-
There's no hook here
So your business is growing and-
27 weeks. This looks like an old one.
Oh, here we go
Ta-da! Okay, you might be going through,
why is Angela holding a light bulb?
Okay, for this, we need to have an audio.
We need mic.
We need a mic. So poor picture,
which this is probably filmed on iPhone.
People are more than willing to forgive,
but when it comes to audio, they are not.
So for instance,
some of you amateurs out there might think
that this is the audio
in which you are listening to me too,
but right now, it's not the case.
What's happening here
is I'm wearing wired headphones so
that the audio from this
doesn't disrupt your viewing pleasure.
And the audio in this
is actually coming from a Sennheiser MKH
416.
There's 500 pound of microphone right
there, let alone the XLR cables going into
the XLR on an FX3. Basically, audio
is tantamount
to your experience watching this right
now, where I've got
that crazy offer in the
description. So if we do not neglect that,
we are not respecting people's ears
and their aural experience.
Not oral as in O-R-A-L.
A-U-R-A-L.
I always hold lots of random things
when I'm talking to my clients.
But the reason for this light bulb
is because-
You've taken too long to get to the point.
Okay, Angela,
one thing you need to work on is hooks.
Things you can say in content straight
away.
So in the first five seconds,
I want people to know what it
is you're about to talk
about and how it solves their problem.
So let's go with a building curiosity
hook.
You've been lied to
when it comes to protein bars.
Straight away,
anyone who kind of wants to know whether
or not they've been lied to
about protein bars will listen.
Everyone that goes,
"I don't eat protein bars" will
leave, but that's fine. Now, that
was my hook.
I now need some kind of setup.
For many years you've been told
that this is a healthy snack.
And I'm here today to say, "Well,
that depends." Then we can move something
else.
There was a study conducted in 2021 where
participants that were on a weight loss
diet, half of them
were given protein bars,
while the other half were made to eat
an apple.
And then you can go into the point,
but that hook talking about you've
been lied to about protein bars,
you're kind of drawing in some people
and pushing
away others. My dad would not stay
and watch a reel about protein bars,
but most of
the fitness industry would.
So you need to go ham and go
through your competitor's best performing
reels, you'll notice there's a good hook.
Rohan. Sprint two distance. Husband
and father, runner and
triathlete. Certified tennis coach.
Okay, if this is a page to grow your
tennis business. Oh,
it's a little bit of everything, actually.
One hour 45.
[panting]
Okay,
we're going to go through the same rules
here. I've never seen you before.
This comes up on my feed.
I'm going away quick.
I feel like I've just walked in on someone
doing something.
What are we doing?
[upbeat music]
I don't like these. Just talk.
Just tell me. Wrong format.
We are here to make-
Don't know what's going on.
So nice
cruisy
20-minute run.
Don't care.
So this morning, we've got
probably-
You see that the nearly three seconds has
surpassed, and nothing has happened
... recovery run. So-
You're just talking about your recovery
run.
Hey, what I need you to do is,
if you're a coach, all right,
and you're a good
coach, is your job to help yourself
or to train yourself? No.
It's about training other people,
and the more you get results for other
people,
the better your business does.
So why would that be different here?
As someone browsing the internet right
now, I'm going to throw it out there.
Unfortunately,
I don't care about your tennis.
I don't care about your triathlons.
I don't care. I care about myself.
But you, as an athlete
and as an experienced
coach,
probably have a lot of knowledge in your
brain that I could benefit from.
So your job on social media
is to share it with me.
And that's
so to keep things-
What's going on here, mate?
I'm just watching a stranger swim with
music.
But every step forward no-
You need to write a list of all the
problems you solve with your clients,
and then
you should solve them on social media.
Good news is you haven't wasted too much
time, but you
are an tech entrepreneur. This page
is not about you. It should be about them.
That's how you're going to get business
out of people. Daniel. Green Monkey Velo.
Custom cycling clothing for road, gravel,
and tri.
Okay,
so we're going to pretend I'm someone
that's never seen your stuff before.
Don't call glimmer wrong.
Bro,
all this shit's like fucking four years
old. Next.
Free home energy upgrades.
Experts in eco grants and EPC
upgrades. I don't know what that means,
mate, to be completely honest.
Cucumber eco.
I don't know what any of this means. Next.
Why send me that?
Not even fucking used it, bruv.
Third Sister RD.
Is that like registered dietitian?
If so, people don't know what that means.
Just going to throw that out there.
They just don't.
As seen in Women's Health
and Stylist Magazine.
I'd rather you said what you did
or specialized in than that.
That can go. Attractive young lady.
Let's have you up here because you
are the brand, not that.
Also, what's your name? Because
when I'm on your page,
I should know what your name
is. Third Sister. What does
that even mean? I don't know.
All day to have a lunch at...
So turns out I have been
quoted in The Grocer, which-
Don't mind this. You do need a microphone
This is how I prep my week with just-
This whispering vibe can go.
I need you as an authority.
If I booked you for a talk to help educate
some trainers on dietetics, you wouldn't
talk like this
... loads of chopped up and roasted-
Sounds like a relaxing meditation.
Unwind in your bath.
What a weekend that was. It
was so incredible just about-
Cool. Appeal to authority.
You're at a speaking event,
or you may be in there
taking it in.
So what is my conclusion from my research
on the blue zones?
Well-
We need to talk with a little bit more
authority here.
I can appreciate
that it's early to content,
but let me give you an example.
When we started Nutonic,
with one thing in mind was the customer,
and we thought, how could we straight away
just don't trust people. I'm like,
"We made the best energy drink on the
market
with five evidence-based ingredients
that you're going to feel
when you take it,
and I'm so sure." The way we speak,
although I don't talk like
that all the time,
but I have to,
to come across as an authority in
training. Now, quickly here.
So what is my conclusion from my research
on-
So what is my conclusion from my research?
You're talking about your conclusion,
your research.
Now,
what I would much rather we had here
was you in the hook going,
what are we talking about here?
Blue zones. Well, first-
What are blue zones?
I don't know what a blue zone is.
So maybe your hook could've been like,
"Do you know about this?
It's called a blue zone, and this
is what blue zones do.
Well, you might not know,
but last week I published a study."
Firstly, there's not one magic answer,
whether
it's, um-
I'm afraid I just don't know what
that means.
So for this article,
I researched quite a bit around-
So if I
don't follow your stuff and I land here...
So imagine we show this to 100 people on
the internet, 99.9% of people don't
know what the fuck's going on.
That's why it's not showing it to a wider
audience.
We need to make sure the content
is ready for everyone in that audience.
So let's say we go to my profile for a
sec.
Hopefully, I don't get embarrassed here.
Actually, I like this sentiment.
Here, hashtags don't do anything,
literally. Hooks.
And everyone's got these real complex
fucking...
This is from a live stream, actually.
Every day, I use this thing right here.
Okay, so there you go. Hook. Every day,
right here, I use this thing to put
together an email that makes you think,
"Hmm, didn't think of that before." So you
know that it's going to be about email
marketing.
It's quite interesting or, hmm,
it's quite funny, actually.
Then at the bottom of that,
I will tell you what I'm working on.
And then I start to give out the format of
how I do an email marketing email.
Do you recommend multiple posts per day
or one good post per day enough?
So there,
I'm using the hook as a question.
Yeah, actually,
there I've got the hook of the question.
There's one thing you'll never see me do,
and that's selling direct on social
media. So every kind of reel,
in the first few seconds,
you kind of know what's
coming and what it's going to be about.
All right, let's go Ethan.
So let's do that.
What I want you to do for your homework
is to ensure that every
single person, at least 50% of them,
will understand the reel, because if they
don't, that's a problem.
Personal trainer and fitness coach.
Would love to know what the difference is.
Built by Bone.
Got to go,
mate. Built by Bone.
Bone means either like a skeleton bone,
or it means to nob someone. Boner. Oh,
I just see built by boners.
Oh, because your surname's Bone. No,
got to go, mate. Ethan Bone.
That's your brand name. Built by Bone. No.
Whoever's idea that was, get rid of them.
Built by Bone.
Mate, they just want to fucking work out.
They want someone to hold them accountable
and teach them shit.
They want someone to make sure they don't
go back to their old ways. Built by Bone.
"Check
the caption." Fuck off.
I don't work for you, mate.
I'm not going to watch your mate eat a
fucking whatever it is
and read your fucking
essay here. If you want to write an essay,
fuck off to Substack. This is Instagram.
71 days till spring. Cool. That, mate,
just fucking make a video.
If that essay you've written there,
that short novel, is that important,
put it in
a fucking video. You know Instagram,
right, is built around people using reels.
Putting that shit on a paperclip fucking
bollocks, mate. You look like a gimp.
No offense.
There's three things you need to think
about when you're deciding how long to
rest
between your sets.
I always set rest periods between sets for
my clients in the
gym.
So there's three things. Fair enough.
You just killed a load of time.
Didn't need that.
With my clients in the gym.
You just sound like a bellend PT.
I'm sorry, mate.
And what's this Built by Bone bullshit
fucking icon up here?
That shit's ass. I'm sorry.
But I tell them it's always just a guide.
If you don't tick these three boxes,
you're not ready for your next set.
Mate, we're like 30 seconds in,
don't know what the fuck you're going to
talk
about.
So why couldn't your hook been how long
should you be resting in the gym?
That's what I think you missed there.
Number one,
is the target muscle still sore?
If you got off a pec deck
and your chest is on fire-
You're not winning me over here, mate.
Like,
what does it take to alleviation of
that feeling from a pec deck?
What, seven seconds? Mate,
stop writing fucking essays over here.
That is your biggest problem. If it's
that important, make a fucking video about
it. Knackered Knackers. Hate it. What
is that?
Knackered Knackers,
male fertility advocate. Oh, I love that.
But do you know what?
Sean Greenaway,
I think that's your business,
not the brand.
I reckon Sean Greenaway is the brand here,
bro.
Knackered Knackers,
because until I see this,
I don't know what it's about.
Because you've got this fertility
business, cool. Be Sean Greenaway.
Sperm donor, recipient, father. Hmm.
Like,
Knackered Knackers can be the business.
Like Chris Williamson is Chris Williamson.
He is not the brand.
He is the brand. Now, all right,
if you're a male fertility advocate,
I hope to
see some content soon.
Supplementation protocols.
We're going to talk about folate, COQ10,
vitamin E, DHA,
EPA. What else have we got in there?
Let's have a look.
Is this a fucking novel or is this a reel?
The pain were very hard that I ever stole.
I played my card-
Sorry,
that's too much text there for my liking.
I don't like these type of reels,
if I'm honest with you.
Time you were really taught about being
infertile was when it
had an actual effect on you. Up until
that point, literally nothing.
Absolutely nothing. Nothing.
Sorry, that's just blown my mind,
because I genuinely didn't know that
that was
even a thing.
Certainly my generation, as a millennial.
Mm-hmm.
I'd like to hope it's changed a bit now,
but back then it was all about how not to
get pregnant.
I do like this. This
is the stuff I want to see.
And like,
you should be starting videos going,
I became a father through sperm donation.
This is something to consider.
I would love you to start content talking
about the facts. I'm making this up.
15% of men over 30 will never be able to
have kids. This is why.
Have you ever considered
that you're infertile?
Because saying that to a group of people,
men aren't having kids till their 30s, we
need to go in on that.
This has performed the best because it's
gone in on that.
It's 50% down to the men.
And I know it sounds obvious-
Yeah
... because we are half the equation, but-
Make this reel again, please.
You've got an obligation here.
There are millions of men who think
they're fertile, don't
respect their fertility, think
that it's all down to the women.
I need you to bring
that to the forefront
and even get in people's faces a bit and
be like, "You could be infertile.
Let me tell you why.
Because at 34,
I thought I'd be able to have kids
and I couldn't.
This is why." Big up on that as a
subject, though. Very, very important.
Let's get through these last ones.
Fast Fire, mate. One post. No chance.
There's a common theme here.
Some people just never get off the mark.
Mitch Moves.
Mobility, strength coach. Movement,
structure, confidence.
Built from anywhere.
Start here. It's not a bad call to action.
Let's get into it.
If these are done correctly,
you will absolutely get a chin up.
First up, be it assisted.
So we're going to get the rings to touch
our chest,
making sure that we squeeze the shoulders
back and down.
Imagine a credit card squeezed between the
shoulder-
I quite like that
If you're doing banded chin-ups,
you're not building the strength you need.
Worse,
if you're just having a crack thinking
you-
Like it
If you're someone who has to always do a
little jump to help you with your
chin-ups, or when you're in this position,
just feels like nothing can happen
Start here with active passive hanging.
We're going to start in a pas-
Like this
In this series,
I'm going to show you the chin-up path
from complete be-
Don't do series.
Just do standalone pieces of content,
because when you say series,
if I've not seen other ones, I'm gone.
You've been doing pistol squats like-
To be able to do a full range pis-
Okay, so one thing I'd love you to do
is rather than having pistol squat season
and
chin-up season and all that,
alternate it through buckets.
Go upper, lower, strength, flexibility.
Upper, lower, strength, flexibility.
Let's get some variation to that.
I think that'd be good. Okay, Rhi.
"Redefined coaching." I like what you've
done
there. I like what you've done there.
Good display pic.
This is a bit cheesy and corny.
It looks like every other fucking coach in
your
niche, and that fat loss coach.
"I help women who've tried everything
except this
drop five to 10 kilograms of belly fat.
Are you finally ready to see results?
Apply form." This is...
It looks quite nice, though.
I'll give you that.
Looks quite nice. I'll give you that.
Give you that. Pretty good.
I'd just rather this
was just a bit more chilled like,
"I help women get in better
shape." I just want to be spoken to.
Have you got a personality?
That's what I want to know, because
if I'm hiring you as a coach,
I want you to be
cool. I want you to have a personality,
and I cannot get any of your
personality across from this.
Let's go. Three, two, one, go!
[upbeat music]
I can see you've got a rig
and a fantastic well-developed set of
derrieres.
Beautiful young lady with an incredible
rig. But don't you think it's an issue?
There's been 17 weeks worth of content.
I don't even know if you're Australian
or if you're English.
I don't know if you're American
or Canadian.
I don't know anything about you.
Talk to camera.
Get your personality across.
Have you ever noticed that all these
fucking women killing it in business all
have personal brands where they talk to
camera?
I'm pretty sure I caught Tay watching some
Molly-Mae shit on
YouTube the other day.
Molly-Mae just doing vlogs,
girls loving her. Loving it.
You go, queen. As much as I admire the
fantastic physique,
I want to get to know who Rhi is.
I want to know something about your
personality.
I want some banter, some idiosyncrasies.
Have you got banter?
Because don't get me wrong,
you got the skills, you got the
physique, you've done the hard part,
right? You're a fox.
But now just do the easy part.
Help me know you.
Let's have a look at your website quick.
Oh,
you check her website because she's
good-looking and got good shape.
No, it's because her social
is pretty good. "Get started." Okay.
Not bad, that. Okay, that's pretty good.
I'll give you that.
Again, could do with a bit of VSL.
I want to know if you've got any
personality.
Can't wait to be in the doghouse for Tay
for saying another bird was fit.
I'm getting to the age now,
I said this to Tay the other day, I
was like, "I can't
even appreciate beauty anymore,"
especially now I'm getting old.
Now I'm 36.
If I see a good-looking 22-year-old,
obviously, I'm just thinking, in my head,
I'm
thinking, "Good work. Well done.
Great parents, good genetics." But if
they're 22 and I'm 36,
they're 14 years younger.
I can't be admiring people 14 years
younger. Okay.
I have no idea what's going on here, mate.
Sorry. Moving on. Dan.
Here we go. Dan King. Coach Dan King.
1,000 posts, 2,000 followers.
You're doing the reps, mate.
That's what I like to see.
"Helping you lose weight so easy it falls
off." Helping
you lose weight I think could be a better
punchline there. Okay, let's have a look.
And we break it down into one-year goal.
And this is where it can get a bit sca-
What's going on here?
Am I watching a podcast or
is this a piece of content?
Because now you're thinking, "Oh shit,
my goals are ridiculous.
How am I going to achieve them?"
Feel like I've just turned up to a podcast
with some terrible music in the
background.
Because if you're a ship in a fucking
ocean and you're going the wrong
direction,
you know-
Who the fuck are you talking to?
Is this a podcast or a piece of content?
If you are genuinely someone
that loves fast food and is a big foodie,
big e-
Mate, I'm not going to lie,
people cringe to this stuff online.
They really do.
You're probably as sick as I am of hearing
these three words.
Hold on. Is that even you?
Because if you're a ship in a fucking
ocean and you're going...
If you are genuinely someone-
You're probably as sick as I-
I don't know. Okay, carry on
... am of hearing these three words,
and that's January fitness challenge.
Because it seems like every coach
and their dog-
I wouldn't sell or promote your challenge
here, mate.
That should be done through your email
marketing list, which reminds me, I've got
to do that, haven't I?
People are always giving themselves a
reason.
I will be careful what I say with
that whole quick fix thing.
So I don't really like this vibe here,
right?
You're sat back.
You're not really engaged. Your legs
are crossed.
You've got quite a defensive posture.
Maybe self-insecurity.
Hiding your eyes from the camera with your
hat. This just ain't it, mate.
Yogs the shit out.
Maybe the next Bradley Martin, but-
People are never going to feel ready,
but it's always when you c-
This stock B-roll shit, it's not working.
Ready, but it's always-
And hash tags don't do anything for me.
Here's your friendly reminder
that you need to chill your chestnuts
when it comes
to losing those post-Christmas kilos
that I know you're so desperate to lose.
Because you can do the ab-
Looking to hire a personal trainer in the
new year?
Here are three green flags to look for-
Not sure on the outfit here either
...
to avoid getting scammed from someone
who's been a personal trainer in the
industry-
Who are you talking to?
If you're thinking about starting in the
gym in the new-
I read this scri-
There's no hooks here.
Here are the three most toxic foods you
can be eating o-
I think what we-
Have you ever heard the saying
that 5K steps keeps the doctor away?
You will-
Would you describe a PT-
Oh, you're going to think I'm mad here,
but ugh.
The camera's got to come up.
You're talking down to me.
That's a problem.
The glasses may have to go.
Just gives you a bit of a nerdy vibe.
And I'm saying this from a place of love.
I wear glasses.
But I don't wear them in content because
as a personal trainer, I don't know what
it is.
You're supposed to come across as fitness.
People don't really wear glasses
when they train.
So I think it's a bit of a thing.
How seriously do I actually take my job
as-
Just stop talking about yourself as a
personal trainer, start solving some
problems.
You've not really solved any problems for
me so far.
There's not one of your videos where I've
gone, "Oh, that's interesting." Or, "Oh,
I didn't think of that before." Or, "Oh,
I didn't know that."
I don't know who needs a virtual slap
around the face,
but your progress in the gym
is not d-
It's very bland. All right.
Let me show you someone. Let's go Ben,
Ben Yanes.
Ben Yanes is a fucking weapon because all
of his videos are really fucking
interesting. Let's have a look.
Most people get the lower trap really
wrong.
Great hook.
Don't do that, okay?
I saw a video the other day of
someone saying this
is what you want to do.
Keep your core straight, tight.
That's your glutes.
Think about it. Wa-pah.
Squeeze a little at the top.
We're flat. We're a table.
So which of these two methods should you
actually do?
The scooping method like this
or the hinging method where your torso
and your legs
move like this?
When you keep your upper body pinned in
one position and you do
this thing that kind of looks like a
twerk, you will be moving through a
combination of spine motion
and hip motion.
So when you arch on the way down,
your hip bends, and
when you curl your butt
underneath of you at the top,
your hip extends or your hip straightens
like this.
So the scoop is spine plus hip motion.
Whereas when you allow your trunk to move
down and up like this, what you're doing
is you're keeping everything from here to
here pretty much fixed, and you're just
isolating the hip motion. And
when you go down like this
and up like this, pretty
much all of this motion just comes from
the hip.
Look at that. That's one video.
He's reacted to one video.
He's recorded that in one take.
Probably took him a few minutes.
I'm learning, you're learning,
everyone's learning.
Fucking 17,000 people here.
Click double like.
Ben Yanes is the master of fucking
delivering good
information, bruv.
That's why his views
are fucking million fucking views on
shit. So when we watch that, we go,
"Right.
Ben Yanes is fucking cooking." He's
educating.
People out there feeling validated,
educated, inspired, fucking
getting rid of misinformation.
You need the Ben Yanes effect in your
content.
None of your videos that I went back
and looked at have that effect.
So people can watch one of his videos
and be different for life.
Someone out there doing a scoop hip thrust
no longer does a scoop hip thrust from
one fucking reel. That
is the level of content you should all
aspire to put
out, and nothing short of that.
If you're not changing lives with your
videos,
which Ben Yanes is doing,
then what's the point?
And the reason that his business will do
well, the reason that his program will
sell is because he set out with
that video to change someone's fucking
life with one reel, and that
is the benchmark you need to survive.
If you want to join my paid program
and get this on a professional level,
there's a
link in the description to an offer
that is far too cheap
that I'm taking offline
in the next few days.
If you want to get roasted,
there's also a link beneath
there, and YouTube recommends
that you should watch this video.
Thank you very much for watching.